{
    "id": "6838fa545d4d4c4aad645cf7847e8fe8",
    "title": "Prepositions",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I look forward to ……………………. from you.",
            "description": "When to is used as a preposition, it is followed by an ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "hear",
                "hearing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She accused me ………………………. reading her letters.",
            "description": "We accuse somebody of something.",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "of",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I completely agree ………………………….. you.",
            "description": "We agree with a person.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I do not agree ………………………… the argument that zoos protect animals.",
            "description": "We agree with an opinion or argument.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I must apologize …………………………. offending you.",
            "description": "We apologize for something.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "about",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I think you should apologize ………………………… him.",
            "description": "We apologize to somebody for something. ",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you believe ………………………… life after death?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The headache prevented me …………………………… studying.",
            "description": "Prevent is followed by object + from + ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "from",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am quite pleased ……………………….. my performance.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "about",
                "at",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "I was hoping that she would pay …………………………. my drink but she didn’t.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "no preposition"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Her marriage ……………………….. her childhood sweetheart did not last long.",
            "description": "Marriage is used with the preposition to.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Nobody knows the reason ………………………… his untimely death.",
            "description": "We use for with reason and of with cause.",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}